♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[muffled shrieking]
[Mongki] They're secured, boss.
I made sure they're sleeping soundly.
Bro, they're going to kill me.
- [Jona squeals]
- [gunshot]
[gunfire blasting]
[Emerson] What do you want?
Burn alive here or get shot outside?!
[Olga] Can you take the child from me?
I'm annoyed with her. She's too nosy.
We'll tell you when to return the child.
[Martina, in English] So,
just deal with her. Okay?
[Paldo] Ouch!
- [screaming and panicking]
- It's Brother Paldo!
[firetruck siren wailing]
[Ibyang] Just give me back to Tatoy!
You're a bad mother!
I'm not a bad mother!
[squeals]
Mama!
[Mona] You look like Adamus.
The guardian of the water gem
- in Encantadia!
- Oh, yes!
He's too handsome compared to me.
[Olga] I thought you
didn't want me anymore
because I'm a bad mother.
I'm here because you are my mama.
I won't be naughty and stubborn anymore.
[Ibyang, in English] Good night, Ma.
[in English] Good night, Ibyang.
[sniffles]
[softly] Go on.
Careful on the stairs, okay?
Yes.
PREVIOUSLY
[music swells]
[music fades]
[Charmi] What happened, friend?
Why does it seem like
you're treating the kid differently?
Huh?
And it's like… Wow.
Why, oh, fantastic, marvelous!
You even cleaned your house.
Are you sure you didn't hit your head?
Oh, want to test it?
Let's roll down the stairs together.
You want to?
Come on. Can't you take a joke?
- Come on.
- Hm-mm.
But you know, in fairness to Ibyang,
she's sweet and thoughtful.
Whoever her parents are,
they're very lucky.
[gentle music playing]
With everything she's been through,
she's still a good child.
It's not hard to love her.
Oh. Aw!
See, that's it.
Why don't you take
being a mother to Ibyang seriously?
Maybe this is the universe's way of giving
you another chance at motherhood.
Oh.
[phone ringing]
Hey! It's Madam.
Go. I'll take it.
Take this.
[mysterious music playing]
Hello, Madam?
Why did you take so long to answer?
Well, you didn't show up.
[smirks]
What did you say?
[titters] Oh, sorry.
Madam, I was just busy.
Okay. So, you said you don't want
Ibyang anymore.
[in English] Well, that's great news.
I think it's time
you give the child back to us.
Right away?
Why? Is there a problem?
[in English] Don't worry.
[in English] You'll have
200,000 pesos bonus.
[in English] I will text you
where we'll meet.
Why? Are you returning her
to her real mother?
[in English] That's none of your concern.
[in English] Just wait for my text.
Okay.
[rousing music playing]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
I'm part of the intelligence unit
conducting the investigation
into the commotion that happened here.
Any information you can give me
regarding the culprits?
Two of our men saw them.
The armed men who stormed in here
were speaking Russian.
[pensive music playing]
They took Lily, our godchild.
[scoffs]
[in English] I'm so sorry.
Anything else your men saw?
They grabbed one man.
One of the tribal dancers.
They said he fought well.
[in English] And I just don't know
why they captured him along with Lily.
[in English] But one of my guards said
he was trying to protect Lily.
Do you think the people
looking for Lily are involved?
She never told me about it.
All I know is she's scared
and feels hounded
by people she won't name.
[music fades]
- [thumps]
- [in English] Talk!
- [in English] Or you will be…
- [grunts]
our punching bag.
- [in English] Every day and every night!
- [Lily whimpers]
[ominous music playing]
[in English] I think
this will make him talk.
[Samir in Russian] Stop it!
[Samir applauds]
[in English] That is enough.
That is enough.
[in English] Hello!
[in English] So, you're not going to talk.
[in English] You're not going to say
where the laptop is.
[sighs]
[in English] No.
[in English] I will make you talk.
[in English] You see,
men like you have a family.
[in English] Maybe you have a wife.
[in English] Maybe you have
a son or a daughter.
[in English] Maybe a dog.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] I have men right now
searching for all of your beloved.
[in English] And when they find them,
they will bring them back here,
and I will kill
every one of them
right in front of your face.
[in English] Or you can tell me
who you work for
and where my laptop is.
[phone rings]
[music swells]
[in English] Update me.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Mission status.
[in English] Outside the establishment.
[in English] Potential headquarters
of Anthony "Atoy" Padua.
[in English] You're just
wasting your time.
[ominous music playing]
[in English] I have no family.
[in English] Everyone has a weakness,
and I will find yours,
and you will regret everything.
[in English] There's nothing
that can hurt me.
[in English] Nothing.
[in English] Is that so, mister?
[clicks]
[music swells]
[grunts]
‪[sighs, gasps]
[in English] How about that? Hmm?
- [in English] How about that?
- [groans]
[in English] Stop! No! No, no.
[whimpering]
[Samir, in English] Well…
[in English] What about this one? Hmm?
[in English] Is she important to you?
[in English] Does she matter to you?
[Atoy, in English] No, no, no! Stop! Stop!
[music intensifies]
[in English] If you kill me now, you will
never be able to open that laptop.
[in English] The ambassador
has all the passwords.
[in English] But it changes every 30 days.
[in English] How would you know the code?
[in English] I'm the only one
who can access it,
and I can erase every classified info
you have on there.
[in English] You know you need me.
[in English] That plan
didn't work out, huh?
[cackles]
[grunts]
[Audrey grunting]
[Janine whimpering]
[suspicious music playing]
[muffled mumbling]
[gasps] Child, untie me.
Quick, faster. Hurry.
Child, child…
- [Janine groans]
- [Audrey shrieks]
[Janine shrieks]
- You're trying to escape?
- [Audrey] What? What will you do to her?!
- You're escaping?!
- [Audrey] Oh, don't hurt her! Red!
Take her!
- No!
- Let me go! Mommy!
- Let go of my child!
- [Janine squeals]
Release her!
[in English] No!
[groans]
[ominous music playing]
- [Audrey sobs]
- [sighs]
Oh, Audrey.
[sobs]
You can't coax anyone here anymore.
Daddy isn't here to help you either.
[Audrey sobs]
So, if you want to live longer,
learn to listen to me.
[in English] You understand?
Huh?
[in English] Yes?
[music intensifies]
- [foreboding music playing]
- [heavy breathing]
- [Janine] Grandpa.
- Janine?
[panting]
- [in English] Are you alright?
- Grandpa, Uncle Red
locked me and Mommy up.
[Janine] We were supposed
to leave for the US,
but Uncle Red stopped us.
Then he locked us up,
and now they took me.
I don't know
where they're taking me, Grandpa.
[mutters]
[in English] Okay, okay.
Janine, go on ahead.
[in English] Go to the garage. Okay?
Grandpa, save Mommy.
[in English] I will. Go!
[in English] Now.
Dad, you shouldn't have let Janine escape.
What did you do to Audrey,
to my granddaughter?!
[pensive music playing]
She's not really your granddaughter.
She's not really Audrey's daughter either.
[tense music playing]
[suspicious music playing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[grunts, panting]
[grunts]
[pensive music playing]
[grunts, panting]
[grunting]
[panting]
[softly] Hurry, hurry.
[grunts, panting]
‪[grunts, panting]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[moans]
[sighs]
[sighing]
[music fades]
She's not really our blood.
What nonsense are you saying, Red?!
[in English] It's simple. Okay?
[in English] Martina and I
faked everything.
[in English] Documents, papers, all of it.
Even the people we talked to,
they were all in on it.
So we could show Audrey
that we found her missing child.
[in English] Okay?
So, you deceived me too?
Why?!
So you'd… So you'd stop!
You kept pressuring us!
You're always thinking about Audrey!
Audrey can't be angry,
Audrey can't be sad!
You don't understand.
Your daughter is manipulating you!
You're becoming a fool
because you kept protecting Audrey!
You're really worthless.
[grunting and groaning]
[thumping and thudding]
[tense music playing]
[softly] So?
You'll shoot me?
You'll shoot me because of Audrey?
- [music fades]
- [sighs]
[suspicious music playing]
[huffs]
[rousing music playing]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
‪[grunts]
[whimpering]
[sinister music playing]
Where is Audrey?
Bring Audrey out!
Go! Shoot me. Go ahead.
[in English] Don't push me, Red.
[in English] Don't push me!
‪[soft gasping]
Admit it.
[music fades]
You'll still side with Audrey, won't you?
Do you know, she was going
to report us to the police?!
I just stopped her!
That's not a reason to lock her up.
I know you've long wanted her gone!
[in English] Yes!
For a long time!
Because she's the only one
you see, right?!
What about me, huh?
Did you ever treat me like your son?
No, right?!
Do you know why?
[pensive music playing]
Do you know why?!
[music intensifies]
What are you proud of?
Your being out of control?!
[in English] Dmitri, enough!
[in English] Red, Red, stop. Don't leave!
Son, you've been drinking.
Let's go inside, please!
For what, Ma?
So he can beat me up again?!
[Dmitri] Let him go!
He only brings us headaches!
[in English] I've had it with him!
[in English] Okay, fine!
[music fades]
I already told you, didn't I?
[in English] I told you to stop!
[in English] Hon. Just let him go.
- Don't waste your effort. Just let him go!
- [in English] No!
- Hon.
- [car engine starts]
Hon. Hon!
Get in.
[music fades]
[screams] I'm always the one at fault!
[car revving]
[ominous music playing]
- [horn honks]
- [tires screeching]
[car crashes]
[tires screeching]
[in English] Mom. Mom!
[in English] Mommy.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain spattering]
- [in English] Mom, Mom!
- [epic music playing]
[in English] Mom! Mom, Mom, Mom…
Help! Help!
[in English] Mom, Mom, Mom…
[tires screeching]
[Red] Help!
Help!
[Dmitri] Hon! Hon!
- Hon! Go! Call an ambulance!
- Mom!
[Dmitri] Hon!
[Red bawls]
- Hon!
- [Red, in English] Mom, please!
- [Dmitri] Hon. Hon. Hon!
- [indistinct]
Hon, no!
Hon!
[in English] Mom, please!
Please wake up, Mom!
[Smitri] Get out of here!
[music fades]
[in English] I lost my wife,
your mother, because of you!
But I still accepted you as my son.
I knew my responsibility to you,
and I fulfilled it,
despite everything!
But you never forgave me!
[Dmitri] You're right!
You're right!
[melancholic music playing]
Every goddamn day,
I wish it was you who died,
not your mom!
She and Audrey,
they're the only ones who matter to me.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[panting]
Audrey!
[grunts]
[groans]
[somber music playing]
[in English] You're going
to shut your mouth now?
[groans]
[in English] Is that it, huh?
[smirks]
[in English] I didn't feel a thing.
[cackles]
[in English] You're going
to get it, sir. Oh yes.
[cackles]
[in English] One more, huh?
- [grunts]
- [Lily wails]
- [groaning]
- That's enough!
[Atoy coughs]
[cackles]
[in English] You think you're tough…
for beating up a tied-up man?
[pensive music playing]
[in English] You're weak, huh?
[in English] You're weak.
[in English] You coward.
Co… ward!
[in English] You Zahranians are weak.
[Atoy, in English] Cowards, huh?
[in English] Do you know what "coward" is?
[in English] Come here.
[imitates a chicken clucking sound]
[cackles]
[in English] Release him!
[in English] Release him now!
[in English] I'm going
to teach this man a lesson!
[in English] Hurry, hurry!
Release him now!
[imitates a chicken clucking sound]
[Atoy whoops]
[in English] I'm going to teach you
something, sir, huh.
[in English] You will regret this
for the rest of your life!
[Atoy cackles]
[groans, whoops]
[in English] Get out of here.
[in English] Get out. Go!
[in English] Stand up and let us fight.
- [tense music playing]
- [grunts]
[in English] Yes, yes.
[in English] Now, we will fight
and see who the tough guy is.
[in English] But remember, if you lose,
I will cut her finger.
[electronic blipping]
[intense music playing]
[Atoy] We won't be able
to get out anymore.
We'll rot here.
Think of the people who love you.
No one cares about me now.
[in English] Kill me now! Now.
This is what you want, right?!
[in English] You're not worth it.
‪UP NEXT
- [Red] You will die!
- [gunshot]
You shouldn't give up.
[Lily] Surely, you left a mark
on at least one person.
[in English] Let's go, coward.
[in English] I'll let you hit me first.
[in English] You need this one.
[grunts]
I forgot you're a demon!
Where is my real child?!
I'll never tell you, even if you shoot me.
- [grunts]
- [shouts]
[grunting]
[grunting and groaning]
[clanging and clattering]
- ["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- [grunts]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias